ROB ROCHE VILLANUEVA

Triplet Street | 09270649427 Sto. Niño Road, Zamboanga City | villanuevarobroche@yahoo.com Filipino | September 3, 2001



· SOCIALS ·

facebook.com/robroche.villanuevaii.9 <u>robroche565.github.io</u>

www.linkedin.com/in/rob-roche-villanueva-7b83472b2

Adept in multiple programming languages for four productive years. Excelled in Python Development. Demonstrated professionalism in collaboration with other Members. Served as a UI/UX and Full-Stack Developer. Graduated from Western Mindanao State University with a strong academic background in a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science.

EDUCATION

Graduate

Aug. 2020 - May 2024 Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Western Mindanao State University

GWA: 1.5497 (Cum Laude)

Secondary

June 2014 - April 2018 Regional Science High School IX

GPA: 87.6

Primary

June 2008 - March 2014 Claret School of Zamboanga City

GPA: 94.6

ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE

July 2023 - April 2024 Al-Driven Syllabus Generation using OpenAl

Language Model for Improving Course Design

Full-Stack Developer

- · Responsible for coding back-end and front-end
- Used GPT-3 as the basis for the web development.
- · Language used Django

Jan. 2023 - April 2023 KENO Gym Management System

UI/UX Developer

- · Responsible for creating graphical interface for users.
- · Responsible for coding the layout.

Nov 2022 - Nov 2022

Prediction on Credit Cards Users Declining the

service based on their Social Status

Data Analyst

Designed and developed a web based system that predicts the Credit Cards Users Declining the service

based on their Social Status

PUBLICATIONS

April 2024 Al-Driven Syllabus Generation using OpenAl

Language Model for Improving Course Design

Using the OpenAl Language Model to

Generate the Syllabus of WMSU.

Specifically the Colleges.

Published in April 2024

Western Mindanao State University

Co-Authors, Daud and Avon

November 2018 Avocado Leaves as an Alternative Fertilizer for

Tomato (Research)

Converting Avocado Leaves into Fertilizer by feeding them to worms and using their

feces as fertilizer for tomato.

Published in November 2018

Regional Science High School

Co-Authors, Ebarle and Cheong

ACTIVITIES

March 22, 2024 Research Colloquium 2024

Research Forum where all Thesis are to be presented with panelists from different sectors in Zamboanga

City.

Western Mindanao State University

Normal Road, Baliwasan 7000 Zamboanga City

Philippines

September 8, 2023 Hack4Gov Cyber Challenge 2023

HackForGov accelerates cyber-proficiency in students, fostering a passion for cybersecurity through real-world problem-solving challenges and preparing top talent to represent the Philippines in international capture-the-

flag competitions.

LM Hotel, Zamboanga City

Philippines

August 26, 2023

Google I/O Extended 2023 Zamboanga Peninsula

Google I/O Extended is a great opportunity for developers of all levels to learn and grow. Whether you're a beginner or an experienced developer.

Garden Orchid, Zamboanga City

Philippines

August 7, 2023

English Proficiency For International Competitiveness

(EPIC)

EPIC breaks down communication barriers to attract and retain global talent, fostering innovation, driving growth, and securing a competitive edge in the global

market.

Western Mindanao State University

Normal Road, Baliwasan 7000 Zamboanga City

Philippines

December 1, 2022

Data Analysis with Python

A course teaches the basics of Python to exploring many different types of data. It teaches how to prepare data for analysis, perform simple statistical analyses, create meaningful data visualizations, predict future trends from data.

Cognitive.ai

November 26, 2022

GDG DevFest Zamboanga Peninsula 2022

DevFest is an annual technology conference that covers important topics for the tech community.

Western Mindanao State University

Normal Road, Baliwasan 7000 Zamboanga City

Philippines

November 28, 2022

Codered: Digital Forensics Essentials (DFE)

Digital Forensics Essentials helps learners increase their competency and expertise in digital forensics and information security skills, thereby adding value to their workplace and employer.

Codered

October 25, 2022

Codered: Network Defense Essentials (NDE)

Network Defense Essentials covers the fundamental

concepts of information security and network

defence.

Codered

October 4-19, 2021 DSC Crimsons Info Session

A training to teach beginners or first time coding

a better way and efficient way of coding.

Developer Student Club Crimsons Western Mindanao State University

Via Google Meet

AWARDS

May 17, 2024 WMSU Graduation 2024

Cum Laude GPA: 1.5497

Western Mindanao State University

Normal Road, Baliwasan 7000 Zamboanga City

Philippines

March 22, 2024 Research Colloquium 2024

Best Thesis Overall.

Western Mindanao State University

Normal Road, Baliwasan 7000 Zamboanga City

Philippines

SKILLS

Programming Languages

C++ HTML

Java Django

Python JavaScript

MySQL Laravel

PHP

LANGUAGES

English Advance Conversational

Filipino Conversational

REFERENCES

Jaydee Ballaho

Professor of WMSU BSCS

jaydee.ballaho@wmsu.edu.ph